Contact

shreveport_07@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/robyn-murray-38b63831 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Acute Care

BLS

Clinical Research

Robyn Murray

Travel Nurse at MedPro Healthcare Staffing

Texas City, Texas

Summary

Experienced Lead Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Critical Care Medicine, Physician Relations, Healthcare Management, Healthcare, and Dialysis. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science focused in Nursing from Northwestern State University.

Experience

MedPro Healthcare Staffing Travel Nurse May 2020 - Present (3 months) Alliance, Nebraska, United States

Axis Dialysis (Formerly Greater Houston Acutes) Lead Nurse October 2012 - Present (7 years 10 months)

Fastaff Travel Nursing
Travel Nurse
November 2019 - May 2020 (7 months)
Greenville, NC

Travel dialysis RN in a large, fast paced acute hospital setting

Us Renal Care Registered Nurse March 2019 - November 2019 (9 months) Houston, Texas, United States

Hemodialysis RN in an acute hospital setting taking care of critical care Cancer patients at MD Anderson Cancer Center

Aya Healthcare
Travel Registered Nurse
February 2018 - December 2018 (11 months)
Greater Milwaukee Area

Travel Acute Dialysis RN covering 10 hospitals

Us Renal Care Charge Nurse June 2017 - February 2018 (9 months) Houston, Texas, United States

Hemodialysis RN at MD Anderson Cancer Center (contracted Dialysis provider originally serviced by Intermedical Healthcare and contract services were assumed by US Renal Care in October 2017)

Crown Dialysis
Facility Administrator
September 2011 - October 2012 (1 year 2 months)
Houston Area, Texas

SNG Sandcastle Dialysis
Facility Administrator
February 2011 - October 2011 (9 months)

Bissonnet Dialysis Nurse Consultant January 2010 - August 2010 (8 months) Houston

Responsible for the retraining of clinical staff in a Level III clinic. Charge RN until staff retrained and ready for state re survey. Responsible for implementation of existing and new policy and procedures.

Dialysis Clinic, Inc.
Nurse Consultant
June 2009 - January 2010 (8 months)
Nacogdoches Texas

Responsible for retraining of clinical staff in a Level III facility. Charge RN until staff trained and ready for state survey. Responsible for implementation of existing and new policy and procedures.

Sandcastle Dialysis
Clinical Nurse Educator
September 2007 - May 2009 (1 year 9 months)
Texas city

Responsible for training new employees in a Level III facility. Responsible for updating and maintaining employee education records as well as

implementation of new policy and procedures. Responsible for retraining of clinical staff ad needed.

DaVita

Facilities Administrator March 2003 - October 2008 (5 years 8 months)

Davita Central and Davita Houston Heights

Midland Dialysis Nurse Consultant June 2002 - 2003 (1 year) Midland Texas

Charge Nurse in some Level III facility. Responsible for training new and existing staff and implementation of new P&P. Assisted in transition from Level III designation to passing state survey and removal of Level designation.

Renal Care Group Charge Nurse June 2000 - May 2002 (2 years) Angleton Texas

Education

Northwestern State University
Bachelor of Science, Nursing · (1989 - 1993)